const questions = [{
  numero: 1,
      question: "Which region are the Knights of Favonius located?",
      answer: ["Khaenriah", "Mondstadt", "Inazuma"],
      rightAnswer: 1
    },
    {
    numero: 2,
      question: "Who are the four beginner characters that you start the game with?",
      answer: ["Venti, Zhongli, Ei, Nahida", "Albedo, Sucrose, Traveler, Bennett", "Traveler, Lisa, Amber, Kaeya"],
      rightAnswer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the pitstop between Mondstadt and Liyue?",
      answers: ["Dihua Marsh", "Wangshu Inn", "Dragonspine"],
      rightAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of your Silver haired flying companion",
      answers: ["Paimon", "Spymon", "Byemon"],
      rightAnswer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "What element does the traveler acquire first in Teyvat?",
      answers: ["Anemo", "Geo", "Electro"],
      rightAnswer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "Which island of Inazuma is known for its Aztec-like story theme?",
      answers: ["Yashiori Island", "Watatsumi Island", "Tsurumi Island"],
      rightAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What are the demon names of the currently confirmed archons?",
      answers: ["Santa, Rudolf, Satan, George, Frank, Jim", "Barbatos, Morax, Beelzebuul, Buer, Focalors, Murata", "Bermuda, Borax, Baal, Beer, Folklore, Murakami"],
      rightAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "How many Fatui Harbingers were there originally (We don't talk about Signora)?",
      answers: ["11", "9", "6"],
      rightAnswer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "Who was it who originally sealed away the traveler and their twin?",
      answers: ["Kiana Kaslana", "The Sustainer of Heavenly Principles", "The Principality of Celestia"],
      rightAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What are the virtues of the currently encountered archons of Teyvat (as of 3.0)?",
      answers: ["Love, Justice, Wisdom, War", "Justice, Transience, Freedom, War", "Freedom, Contracts, Eternity, Wisdom"],
      rightAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "The Tianquan of the Liyue Qixing is?",
      answers: ["Keqing", "Qiqi", "Ningguang"],
      rightAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the cell in which Nahida was imprisoned?",
      answers: ["Sanctuary of Samsara", "Sanctuary of Suresthana", "Sanctuary of Shamshir"],
      rightAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the First descender?",
      answers: ["Celstia", "Phanes", "Traveler"],
      rightAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the princess of Sal Vindagnyr's protector?",
      answers: ["Irminsul", "Imunlaukr", "Imminent"],
      rightAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Who was responsible for the sacrifice of King Deshret?",
      answers: ["Greater Lord Rukkhedevata", "Himself", "Lesser Lord Kusanali"],
      rightAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Before the First Who Came, who, or what, were the original inhabitants of Teyvat?",
      answers: ["Celestia", "Orobashi", "Dragonheirs of the Depths"],
      rightAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of Albedo's brother, also created by Rhinedottir?",
      answers: ["Durin", "Dvalin", "Daran"],
      rightAnswer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the creator of the Dainichi Mikoshi?",
      answers: ["Aberaku", "Supada", "Daimon"],
      rightAnswer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "The origin of the Black Serpent Knights is?",
      answers: ["The Chasm", "Enkanomiya", "Khaenriah"],
      rightAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What are the names of the Moon Sisters?",
      answers: ["Seelie, Hili, Canon", "Aria, Sonnet, Canon", "Aria, Seelie, Hili"],
      rightAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "The Guili Assembly of Liyue was ruled by which god?",
      answers: ["Zhongli", "Havria", "Guizhong"],
      rightAnswer: 2,
    },
  ];

module.exports = { questions };